{
    "subject": "resource/East_Germany",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/East_Berlin",
    "human_readable": "East Germany's capital is East Berlin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8703436255455017,
            "question": "Were there any other capitals in East Germany besides East Berlin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8373579382896423,
            "question": "Where was the capital of East Germany located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8177165389060974,
            "question": "What was the capital of East Germany?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7990447282791138,
            "question": "Is Berlin the capital of a former German state?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5490962862968445,
            "question": "What is the name of the former country that had Berlin as its capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5389134287834167,
            "question": "What happened to East Berlin after German reunification?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4443468749523163,
            "question": "Was East Berlin a major city during the Cold War?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3681298792362213,
            "question": "When was East Germany formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2704530656337738,
            "question": "What were some key characteristics of East Berlin during the Cold War?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06551731377840042,
            "question": "Can you name other cities in Germany that were significant during the Cold War?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=East Germany's capital is East Berlin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8964_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some key characteristics of East Berlin during the Cold War?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8964_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was East Germany formed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8964_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was East Berlin a major city during the Cold War?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8964_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8964_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8964_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8964_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8964_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8964_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8964_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8964_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8964_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8964_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8964_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information clearly states that \"East Berlin was the capital of East Germany until the fall of the Berlin Wall in 1989\" and also mentions that \"East Berlin remained the capital of the GDR, while a new West German capital was established far to the west, in Bonn.\" This supports the statement that East Germany's capital is indeed East Berlin."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that \"East Berlin was the capital of East Germany until the fall of the Berlin Wall in 1989,\" directly supporting the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}